<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE some_name [ 
<!ENTITY nbsp "&#160;">
<!ENTITY copy "&#169;">
<!ENTITY epsilon "&#949;">
]>

<page>
  <title>Contribute to the MOEA Framework</title>
  <description>Learn how to contribute to the MOEA Framework</description>
  <header></header>
  <content>
<h2>Contribute</h2>
  
<p>
  Contributions from the community are the backbone of open source projects.
  We welcome all individuals who wish to help develop or provide support for
  the MOEA Framework.
</p>

<div class="section">
<h3>Requirements</h3>

<p>
  In order to maintain a quality product, it is necessary to mandate certain
  requirements on source code contributions (including associated data files and
  other resources).
</p>
  
  <ul>
    <li>
      All contributions must adhere to and be licensed under the 
      <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl.html">GNU Lesser General Public
      License</a> (GNU LGPL), version 3 or later.  The contributor must also ensure 
      that any individual, school or business which may own the rights
      to any part of the contribution agrees to license under the GNU LGPL.
    </li>
    <li>
      All contributions must be fully documented.  As the MOEA Framework is
      academic in nature, the documentation should include citations to the
      original works describing the contribution.
    </li>
    <li>
      The contribution must have academic value.  This means that preference is
      given to works which are published in scientific, peer-reviewed 
      literature.
    </li>
    <li>
      Whenever possible, the contribution should be fully tested using 
      <a href="http://www.junit.org/">unit tests</a>.  Tests should cover
      all non-trivial code whose correctness is not immediately obvious.
    </li>
    <li>
      The implementation should follow software best practices, favor clear
      and understandable source code, and follow the general formatting and
      structure of existing code.
    </li>
  </ul>
</div>

<div class="section">
<h3>Where to Start</h3>

<p>
  If you are interested in contributing to the MOEA Framework, first download
  the source code for the latest version.
  The TODO document distributed with the source code lists about 20 easy tasks
  that newcomers can tackle.  Also check the bug and feature request trackers
  on the <a href="support.html">support</a> page.  
</p>

<p>
  We also encourage new contributors to sign up at our
  <a href="https://openhatch.org/+projects/MOEA%20Framework">OpenHatch</a>
  page by clicking the 'I want to help' button below.
</p>

<style>
    @import url('http://openhatch.org/static/css/tipsy.css?1268950194.0');
</style>

<style type="text/css">
#openhatch-wannahelp-button { background: #C8E29D url('http://openhatch.org/static/images/wannahelp-button-bg.png?1268950194.0') repeat-x scroll center top; display:block; -webkit-border-radius: 8px; -moz-border-radius: 8px; border-radius: 8px; padding: 10px 20px; color: #444; border: 3px solid #fff; white-space: normal; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; width: 250px; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; float: center; font-weight: normal; cursor: pointer; cursor: hand; text-align: center; text-shadow: 0px 1px 0px #fff; background-color: #c8e29d; background-repeat: repeat-x; background-position: top; font-size: 13pt; }
#openhatch-wannahelp-button:active { background-image: url('http://openhatch.org/static/images/wannahelp-button-bg-hover-active.png?1268950194.0'); background-position: bottom; }
#openhatch-wannahelp-button:hover, #openhatch-wannahelp-button:focus { background-image:url('http://openhatch.org/static/images/wannahelp-button-bg-hover.png?1268950194.0'); text-decoration: none; color: #222; }
</style>

<form method="POST" action="http://openhatch.org/+do/project.views.wanna_help_do" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;">
    <input type="hidden" name="from_offsite" value="True" />
    <input type="hidden" value="9423" name="project"/>
    <input type="submit" value="I want to help" rel="tipsy-south" id="openhatch-wannahelp-button" original-title="Click to add yourself to the list of people who want to contribute. People of all levels are welcome!"/>
</form>

<script type="text/javascript" src="http://openhatch.org/static/packed/selections_for_widget.js?1295813773"></script>
</div>

<div class="section">
<h3>Submitting Contributions</h3>

<p>
  Please submit contributions you would like included in the main release to
  <a href="mailto:contribute@moeaframework.org">contribute@moeaframework.org</a>.
  Individuals wishing to join this project as a core developer should also
  contact us at this e-mail.
</p>
</div>
  </content>
</page>
