<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE some_name [ 
<!ENTITY nbsp "&#160;">
<!ENTITY copy "&#169;">
<!ENTITY epsilon "&#949;">
]>

<page>
  <title>Support for the MOEA Framework</title>
  <description>Submit bugs or request new features for the MOEA Framework</description>
  <header>
    <script type="text/javascript" src="scripts/jquery-1.7.2.min.js"></script>
    <script type="text/javascript" src="fancybox/jquery.fancybox-1.3.4.pack.js"></script>
    <script type="text/javascript" src="fancybox/jquery.easing-1.4.pack.js"></script>
    <script type="text/javascript" src="fancybox/jquery.mousewheel-3.0.4.pack.js"></script>
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="fancybox/jquery.fancybox-1.3.4.css" type="text/css" media="screen" />
    <script type="text/javascript">
      $(document).ready(function() {
        $("a.popup").fancybox({'maxWidth':600, 'maxHeight':400, 'autoDimensions':false, 'type':'inline'});
      });
    </script>
  </header>
  <content>
<h2>Support</h2>

<p>
  The source code and issue tracker for the MOEA Framework is available on
  <a href="https://github.com/MOEAFramework/MOEAFramework/">Github</a>.  Please
  use the links below to report issues.
</p>

<div class="section">
<h3>Report Issues</h3>

<p>
  The MOEA Framework is not bug-free, nor is any other software application,
  and reporting bugs to developers is the first step towards improving the
  reliability of software.  Critical bugs will often be addressed within days.
  Requests for new features will also be considered.
</p>

  <ul>
    <li>
      <a href="https://github.com/MOEAFramework/MOEAFramework/issues">
        View Current Issues
      </a>
    </li>
    <li>
      <a href="https://github.com/MOEAFramework/MOEAFramework/issues/new">
        Submit New Issue
      </a>
    </li>
  </ul>
</div>

<div class="section">
<h3>Professional Support</h3>

<p>
  For businesses, we offer professional consulting and support services.  This
  can include <a href="#training" class="popup">web-based or onsite training</a>,
  <a href="#custom" class="popup">custom software development</a>,
  <a href="#phone" class="popup">9-5 EST phone support</a>, and more.  Please contact
  <a href="mailto:support@moeaframework.org">support@moeaframework.org</a> for
  more information or to request a quote.
</p>
</div>

<div style="display:none">
  <div id="training">
     <h2>Web-based or Onsite Training</h2>
     <p>
       Our experts can provide web-based or onsite training for your employees
       using the MOEA Framework.  Topics can range from the installation and
       use of the MOEA Framework, advanced use of multiobjective optimization,
       and more.  One day training sessions include:
       <ul>
         <li>6 hours of interactive training per day</li>
         <li>Up to 10 participants</li>
         <li>Walkthrough coding, compiling, and running examples</li>
         <li>Question and answer sessions</li>
         <li>Free digital copies of the user guides for all participants</li>
       </ul>
     </p>
     <p>
       Contact us at <a href="mailto:support@moeaframework.org">support@moeaframework.org</a>
       to schedule your training or request a quote.
     </p>
   </div>
</div>

<div style="display:none">
  <div id="custom">
     <h2>Custom Software Development</h2>
     <p>
       We understand your time is valuable.  Learning and integrating a new
       technology into your business can be costly.  That's why you can offload
       your development costs to us.  Our experts will work with your team
       to develop system requirements, deliver high-quality software, and
       provide extended support.  We offer:
       <ul>
         <li>Deliver high-quality software based on your requirements</li>
         <li>Onsite training and integration of software (if necessary)</li>
         <li>Support and bug fixes up to one year after delivery</li>
         <li>Extended support options for bug fixes and support up to 5 years</li>
       </ul>
     </p>
     <p>
       Contact us at <a href="mailto:support@moeaframework.org">support@moeaframework.org</a>
       to learn more about what we can offer.
     </p>
   </div>
</div>

<div style="display:none">
  <div id="phone">
     <h2>9-5 Phone Support</h2>
     <p>
       We offer free support via Github's issue tracker, but response times may
       vary.  With 9-5 Phone Support, our experts are available 9-5 EST Monday
       through Friday to respond to your issues either by phone or web
       conference.  In addition to responding to any questions, we also
       address any bugs or issues identified and provide you immediate access
       to the patch.  Support includes:
       <ul>
         <li>Up to 50 support calls a year</li>
         <li>First access to bug fixes and patches</li>
         <li>Call our domain experts any weekday to help troubleshoot issues</li>
         <li>Basic software and integration support (does not include custom software development)</li>
       </ul>
     </p>
     <p>
       Contact us at <a href="mailto:support@moeaframework.org">support@moeaframework.org</a>
       to request a quote.
     </p>
   </div>
</div>

  </content>
</page>
